[{"answer": "I think that their feeling is look, first, they had to put it out in public because they were closing so many U.S. embassies.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Do you think that they were on top of this and managed to stop something from happening?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Piers, I think it can't be understated.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "What is the significance do you think of this?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "No, Piers.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Have they perhaps caused a bigger problem going forward?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you're on this roller coaster certainly with the death of his wife and son that had to be, I would almost say, catastrophic, and then to not know whether your daughter was still alive or not for a period of time, you know, we had that roller coaster effect emotionally that, you know, we would hear that a body had been found or a burned body or bones or, you know, any type of scenario out there.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Obviously, a very happy ending to this, as indeed it was in your case, but tell me how you feel about what he's been going through and what advice you would give them as a family going forward?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "We're in negotiation stages with the individual that's in the bank.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "What is the latest in the situation down there?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, we do understand that he is armed.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "And do you believe that he is heavily armed?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, I'm attracted to these stories on gun sales as in Virginia, as into other states that you mentioned because they demonstrate that more guns equal less crime, and I think it's important that we understand that when you or President Obama or whoever supports forcibly disarming the American citizenry, we make the vulnerable more vulnerable.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "This situation in Newtown, is it not disconcerting that in the very place where we saw this horrendous massacre that we see such a spike in gun sales?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's a great question.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Why not America?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Why don't we take a woman who was in this very position, a woman who armed herself to the teeth, as it turned out, to protect herself exactly in the way that you're talking about.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Would you want your wife to be armed were she in that position?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "No, I haven't looked at those stats on that.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "In America?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Well, no, because here is the point, Mr. Hawkins.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Can I say one other thing, Piers?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "- the highest murder rate in the country.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "And you know what the good news is?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "It's not unthinkable.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Is it unthinkable, S.E., that he could he could just fast-tracked to become a Democratic presidential nominee even as early as 2016?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Look, the Atlantic had a piece recently and Congressional Research Center also has debunked this.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "What do we make of this, S.E.?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Look, I -- I don't believe that fairness should be a -- a motivating factor for law enforcement.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "S.E. Cupp, what is your view of stop and frisk?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, they're upset because it's Oprah.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "But what do you think of this particular incident where the Swiss are pretty upset about it?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Really.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Well, clearly, she didn't want to talk about it in public because she's backtracking now.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What should she have done?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Well, no one asked her to talk about it.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "What should she have done instead of talking about it?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Absolutely, she's -- she's -- she's welcome to.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Would that satisfy you?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "That's true.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Do we all agree?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Absolutely terrifying, absolutely surreal.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Is it absolutely terrifying?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "He's absolutely a hero.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "And how important was the man standing to your left, Richard Shanley who has emerged as one of the great heroes of what happened?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "No, sir, I didn't think about that.", "docId": "130813pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Did you feel at the time that you, yourself may not get out of this alive?", "qSentId": 616}]